<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MatDaan</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">open navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="title_activity_split">Split</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="Open" />
    <string name="Close" />
    <string name="description_bjp"><b>AGRICULTURE</b>\

Launch a pension scheme for small and marginal farmers to ensure social security after 60 years of age. \

• Strive to ensure all-weather connectivity for every village. \

• Work towards digitising land records.\


YOUTH AND EDUCATION \

• Aim to cover all the secondary schools under Operation Digital Board. \

• Enable investment of . 1 lakh crore in higher education through Revitalising of Infrastructure and Systems in Education (RISE). \

• Work towards increasing the number of seats in premier management institutes.\

INFRASTRUCTURE \

• Ensure a pucca house to every family. \

• Ensure the LPG gas cylinder connection to all poor rural households. \

• Ensure 100% electrification of all households. \

RAILWAY \

• Ensure conversion of all viable rail tracks to broad gauge by 2022. \

• Make all efforts to ensure electrification of all railway tracks by 2022. \

• Start developing smart railway stations across India. \

ECONOMY \

• Further improve India’s rank in ‘Ease of Doing Business’ ranking. \

• Work towards improving GDP share from manufacturing sector. \

• Work towards doubling the total exports.\
    </string>
    <string name="narendra_damodardas_modi">NARENDRA DAMODARDAS MODI</string>
    <string name="des_congress">JOB CREATION\
        • Another key promise by the Congress party revolves around job creation and eradicating unemployment.\
        • According to the manifesto, the Congress party plans to fill up 22 lakh vacancies by March 2020. \
       • Over 10 lakh of those jobs would be provided in Gram Panchayats. \
        • The party has also said that it would grant interest-free loans for the youth of the country for 3 years ahead of a new venture.\
        NYAY SCHEME \
        • The Congress reiterated its determination to introduce NYAY scheme, \
       • under which 20 per cent of India poorest or around 5 crore poorest households will get Rs 6,000 as minimum income per month.\
       • Therefore, each family will get Rs 72,000/annum. According to the party manifesto, it is a direct transfer benefit scheme. \
       • The scheme is likely to cost Rs 3.6 lakh crore per annum.
         6 per cent of GDP for education\
        • The Congress party has also mentioned in its manifesto that at least 6 per \
       • cent of the country GDP will be invested for enabling education for all.\
    </string>

    <string name="des_bsp">
         • Mayawati announced recently that she will build a grand statue of the Hindu deity Parashurama —a Brahmin \
        •  We will work on the policy of sarvjan hitay, sarvjan sukhayon coming to power.\
        • Mayawati, however, said the coalition of opposition parties, if it formed the government at the centre after elections,\
        would deliver better governance than what the Congress and the BJP governments had done in the last seven decades.\
         •On the possibility of her emerging as the prime ministerial candidate, the BSP chief said there was no hurry to decide on the PM candidate. \
        Let the elections be over first. The PM candidate will be decided only after elections.
    </string>

    <string name="des_cpi">
    • The party that has helmed many farm movements in the last five years has promised in its manifesto that minimum support price should be 50% higher than the total cost of production.\
    •The manifesto also promises a long standing demand of the trade unions that the statutory minimum wage should be fixed not less than ₹18,000 per month.\
      •The party has promised a host of measures to defend democratic rights including working towards repealing laws such as the Sedition Law, Armed Forces Special Powers Act\(AFSPA), National Security Act (NSA) and defamation law.
    </string>


    <string name="des_tmc">
         •We will reserve 80 per cent jobs in industries for locals by bringing a legislation and separate policy for the same to ensure that it is implemented. This will help in addressing unemployment,\
       •Maharashtra already has a regulation for all industries that avail of incentives from the state government to employ 80 per cent local residents in non-supervisory roles and 50 per cent in supervisory roles.\
         •Also on the cards are a Marathi language university, a cultural university in Nashik to preserve Marathi literature, folk art, culinary styles and so on, a low-cost ‘Marathi asmita’ tablet loaded with classical Marathi literature and at least one Marathi language library in every gram panchayat jurisdiction in Maharashtra.
    </string>
    <string name="des_ncp">
         •We will reserve 80 per cent jobs in industries for locals by bringing a legislation and separate policy for the same to ensure that it is implemented. This will help in addressing unemployment,\
       •Maharashtra already has a regulation for all industries that avail of incentives from the state government to employ 80 per cent local residents in non-supervisory roles and 50 per cent in supervisory roles.\
         •Also on the cards are a Marathi language university, a cultural university in Nashik to preserve Marathi literature, folk art, culinary styles and so on, a low-cost ‘Marathi asmita’ tablet loaded with classical Marathi literature and at least one Marathi language library in every gram panchayat jurisdiction in Maharashtra.
    </string>

</resources>